infocusindia.co.in 2018-07-14

# Privacy and Policy

                                           Privacy and Policy
The following information describes how InFocus India would collect and use your personal information
to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information.
                                           Information Collection
InFocus India fully respects your privacy, and shall spare no effort to protect your personal information.
Generally, you will not be required to provide any personal information for browsing this Website.
In order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, some pages on this Website may use cookies,
which are small text files that a site transfers to a user’s (visitor’s) hard disk or browser for added
functionality or for tracking site usage. InFocus India may use cookies to log your IP address and to
determine the path users take on our site and to identify repeat users of our site, but we do not link your IP
address to your personal information. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when
they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser permits.
For specific purposes, in case you provide your name, gender, category and number of credentials, date of
birth, country, title, occupation, contact details, services or information desired, customer code and other
similar personal information that are required for registration or reading E-information by voluntarily
filling in forms, you will be deemed having understood and accepted the use of your personal information
and agreed that InFocus India uses your personal information for the specific purposes.
                                What information do we collect about you?
Information about your use of the Services
In addition to the information you provide, we may collect information about your use of our Services
through software on your device and other means. For example, we may collect:
Device information:-such as your hardware model, IMEI number and other unique device identifiers,
MAC address, IP address, operating system version, and settings of the device you use to access the
Services.
Log information:-such as the time and duration of your use of the Service, search query terms you enter
through the Services, and any information stored in cookies that we have set on your device.
Location information:-such as your device’s GPS signal or information about nearby WiFi access points
and cell towers that may be transmitted to us when you use certain Services. Other information about your
use of the Services, such as the apps you use, the websites you visit, and how you interact with content
offered through a Service.
                                        Use of Information Collected

InFocus India will not sell or rent your personal information at any time under any circumstance. Your
personal information will only be used for InFocus India business purposes such as, to meet your requests
for certain products, documentation and/or services, to send solicited information, to process an order, to
conduct a transaction, to handle a job application or to perform market research. Your personal information
may     be    shared    with   other   InFocus    India   offices    or   subsidiaries   around    the   world.
However, InFocus India may provide certain portion of your personal information to law executive organs
and government authorities as so requested; and InFocus India might disclose certain portion of your
personal information within a strictly limited scope of recipients when InFocus India reasonably thinks it is
necessary for protecting InFocus India, its customers or the public. You shall have foreseen and agreed to
the occurrence of such events when you provide your personal information.
                                                    Cookies
We, as well as certain third parties that provide content, advertising, or other functionality on our Services,
may use cookies, beacons, and other technologies in certain areas of our Services.
Cookies
Cookies are small files that store information on your computer, TV, mobile phone or other device. They
enable the entity that put the cookie on your device to recognise you across different websites, services,
devices, and/or browsing sessions. Cookies serve many useful purposes. For example:
Cookies can remember your sign-in credentials so you don’t have to enter those credentials each time you
log on to a service.
Cookies help us and third parties understand which parts of our Services are the most popular because they
help us to see which pages and features visitors are accessing and how much time they are spending on the
pages. By studying this kind of information, we are better able to adapt the Services and provide you with
a better experience. Cookies help us and third parties understand which ads you have seen so that you
don’t receive the same ad each time you access a Service. Cookies help us and third parties provide you
with relevant content and advertising by collecting information about your use of our Services and other
websites and apps.
When you use a web browser to access the Services, you can configure your browser to accept all cookies,
reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu
of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. The operating system of your device may
contain additional controls for cookies. Please note, however, that some Services may be designed to work
using cookies and that disabling cookies may affect your ability to use those Services, or certain parts of
them.
                              Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties
InFocus India may share your personal information with its business partners to better fulfill your requests
for products and/or services. Certainly, InFocus India will only share your personal information with its
business partners with your consent. If you do not wish to receive marketing materials from any of InFocus

India’s business partners, please do not provide your contact information via the Internet or you may
directly require them to remove your information from their contact list.
                                       Securing Your Information
InFocus India has endeavoured to take commercially reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access
to and improper use of your personal information collected by registered or any other means mentioned
above via your use of this Website. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure
the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every possible precaution to
protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination
of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.
                                      Supporting Children’s Privacy
InFocus India’s Websites do not target, and are not intended to attract children under the age of 13.
InFocus India does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 or send
them requests for personal information.
